vrworld.com 2010-06-11

# cwonline.com - privacy and policy

At **CyberWorld, Inc.** , we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and the users of our Site. This Privacy Policy Statement sets out our policy on the gathering and use of information on this Site. 

Please note that this Privacy Statement applies only to this Site and not to websites of other companies or organizations to which this Site is linked. Although you are not required to register to access this Site, you may be asked to provide us with personal information when you visit certain sections of the Site or enter contests. 

**How does CyberWorld, Inc. use information gathered about its online visitors?**   
Any consumer information gathered on this Site may be used for aggregate research, promotional purposes and/or for future site development. In particular we may use information gathered about you for the following purposes: to send you or, where appropriate, your organization, information about us and promotional material about our products together with details of any offers we may have available from time to time; to monitor interest in our range of products and to assist us to tailor the content of our Site to your needs by collecting information about your preferences through tracking patterns of page views on this site; and to create a profile relating to you in order to show you the content that might be of interest to you and to display the content according to your preferences. 

**Disclosure of Information**   
CyberWorld, Inc. will not disclose personal identifiable information that you provide on this Site to any third parties other than to a CyberWorld agent, except: i) in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy statement, or ii) to comply with valid legal requirements such as law, regulation, warrant, subpoena or court order. 

**Cookies**   
CyberWorld, Inc., in common with many website operators, may use standard technology called cookies on this Site. Cookies are small data files that are downloaded onto your computer when you visit a particular website. You can disable cookies by turning them off in your browser, however, some areas of this Site may not function properly if you do so. 

**Policies for Online Visitors Under 13 Years of Age**   
CyberWorld, Inc. does not provide any personal identifiable information to any third party (other than CyberWorld agents) from our online visitors identified as being under 13 years of age. E-mail addresses of children under 13 are used to deliver requested information. 

When an online visitor under 13 years of age registers or provides any personal identifiable information, he/she is required to provide the e-mail address (or on some Sites, the postal address) of his/her parent or guardian. We will give the parent or guardian notice via e-mail (or postal mail) when their child under 13 years of age registers or provides personal identifiable information. The notification provides the parent or guardian with instructions on how to review and delete information collected from his/her child. 

Although online visitors under 13 years of age may be allowed to participate in some contests or promotions, if such a visitor wins, notification and prizes will be sent to the parent or guardian identified when the child entered the contest or promotion. 

**Security**   
This Site incorporates appropriate safeguards using industry standard technology to heighten the security, accuracy and privacy of any personal information we have collected and we have put in place reasonable precautions to protect information from loss and misuse. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as required. 

**Policy Change**   
If we alter our privacy policy, any changes will be posted on this page of our Site so that you are always informed of the information we collect about you, how we use it and the circumstances under which we may disclose it. Please check back from time to time to ensure you are aware of our current privacy policy. 

We appreciate your interest and hope that you enjoy visiting the Site. 

**Contact Details**   
If at any time you wish to contact CyberWorld, Inc. with any question, complaint, or to exercise any of the rights set out in this privacy policy statement you may do so by contacting CyberWorld, Inc. by the method set out below: 

**Postal Address**   
60 De Bresoles Unit 202   
Montreal, Quebec, Canada   
H2Y-1V5  
tel: +1.514.318.3171  
fax: +1.888.725.8117 

**E-mail**
